

I have a love for problem solving and critical thinking and am not afraid to go the extra mile to solve problems that I have not encounterd before. I strive to work to the best of my abilities consistantly and refuse to cut corners. I have years of experience working as a team to communicate issues and resolve them backed by a strong ability to produce excellent customer satisfaction.

Professional Experience

 $Lube\ Technician \quad \hbox{Black's Tire \& Auto Service, Wilmington, NC | October 2014 - July 2015 }$

- Basic automotive maintence including but not limited to: oil changes, tire rotations / replacement, battery testing / replacement
- Maintaing a clean work enviroment
- · Upkeep of shop equipment

Automotive Mechanic Wilmington Tire & Auto, Wilmington, NC | September 2015 - May 2021

- Actively listened to customers' requests, confirming full understanding before addressing concerns.
- · Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.
- Produced estimates for repairs by sourcing parts and correct labor times.
- Delivered vehicle repairs to customers within specific timeframes.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- · Trained new-hires basic automotive skills to quickly and correctly perform at levels expected of an entry level technican.

Education

High school diploma East Wake High School at Wendell, NC | September 2010 - June 2014

 $\textbf{Certification of Something in Full Stack Web Development} \quad \textbf{University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC | August 2021 - Present Carolina at Chapel Hill At C$

Created full stack web applications through the use of HTML, CSS and Javascript with the use of NodeJS and Express.

Key Skills

- · Critical thinking
- · Reading comprehension
- · Basic math
- · Multitasking abilities

Software